Contact

13d Yenegou Lane D.S.C Housing Complex Warri, Delta state +234 811 27 350 98 (Home) scofield@learnhub.africa

www.linkedin.com/in/idehenscofield (LinkedIn) Learnhub.africa (Company)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

Microsoft Azure Security
Technologies (AZ-500) Cert Prep: 3
Manage Security Operations

ICSI | CNSS Certified Network Security Specialist

Azure Administration: Identities and Governance

Become an Azure Security Engineer

Honors-Awards

CompTia CERTMaster Learn COurse

Publications

The social physiological principal of mindset

Scofield Idehen

Solidity || Cloud Computing || Python || Secuirty Delta

Summary

Creative and analytical Security Specialist, with sufficient working experience in Linux Configuration, Python Framework, Cloud Computing, and Solidity.

Using my knowledge within this field to develop and build world-class projects that are fault-tolerant and security inclusive.

I am detailed and committed and above all, I enjoy simplicity as I believe creating solutions are as important as the process alongside.

Follow my progress b clicking the link https://github.com/Scofield-Idehen to see some of my projects.

I enjoy reading and contributing to open-source.

Experience

LinkOrion Technology Ltd Chief Operations Officer February 2016 - Present (5 years 11 months) Nigeria

Planning, development, and execution of digital programs and campaigns including, SEO/SEM, email, social media, mobile and display campaigns

- Design, build and maintain LinkOrion social media presence. Including management of digital touchpoints, homepage and landing pages
- Increase brand awareness, promote company's products and drive prospects to conversion
- Initiate effective marketing campaigns online and translate business goals into successful marketing campaigns
- Ensure integrated marketing communications for all campaigns. Leverage events, PR, conferences, seminars and exhibitions online on relevant social media channels

- Measure and report performance of all digital marketing campaigns
- Evaluating customer research, market conditions, and competitor data
- Evaluate emerging technologies, keep the company at the forefront of digital media.
- Provide thought leadership and perspective for adoption on online brand communication
- Identify trends and insights, optimize spend and performance based on the insight
- Collaborate with agencies and other vendor partners
- Brainstorm new and creative growth strategies
- Utilize strong analytical ability to evaluate end-to-end customer experience across multiple channels
- Responsible for planning and budgetary control of all digital marketing

LearnHub.Africa
Co-Founder
June 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months)

warri delta state nigeria

Design and build Holistic schemes for start-up Help structure business model for SMES Promote SMEs using SEO

MusicFameWorld.com Marketing Consultant April 2012 - 2014 (2 years)

I help promote and create platforms for the development and showcasing of young upcoming artist.

Education

University of Benin

Bachelor of Arts (BA), International realation and diplomacy · (2010 - 2015)

Technical high school nigeria School leaving certificate, art · (2004 - 2010)